export const questions = [
    { question: 'Question 1?', answer: '1' },
    { question: 'Question 2?', answer: '2' },
    // { question: 'Question 3?', answer: '3' },
    // { question: 'Question 4?', answer: '4' },
    // { question: 'Question 5?', answer: '5' },
    // { question: 'Question 6?', answer: '6' },
    // { question: 'Question 7?', answer: '7' },
    // { question: 'Question 8?', answer: '8' },
    // { question: 'Question 9?', answer: '9' },
    // { question: 'Question 10?', answer: '10' }
]
